[Music]
this thing
on hey Miss PS if you find this
recording don't feel bad about
this part of the journey is the
end just the record Being a drift in
space with zero promise of rescue is
more fun than it
pounds food and water ran out 4 days
ago oxygen will run out Tom longrow
morning that be
it when I drift off I will dream about
you it's always you
[Music]
Thanos did exactly what he said he was
going to
do he wiped
out 50% of all living
creatures we lost all of
us we lost friends we lost family
we lost a part of
ourselves this is the fight of our
lives this is going to work
Steve I know it is cuz I don't know what
I'm going to do if it doesn't
hi uh is anyone home this is Scott Lang
we met a few years ago at the airport in
Germany got got really big is this an
old message Ant-Man and I know you know
I know you know that it's the front door
that's me Can you buzz me in